Guide to the New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences. Office of Academic Programs records, [ca.1875]-1981.
New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences. Office of Academic Programs records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences. Office of Academic Programs records, [ca.1875]-1981.
21-3-1304
New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences. Office of Academic Programs.
15 cubic ft.
Manuscripts, Printed documents
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes surveys of graduates and records of the Cornell Office of Resident Instruction.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
Prior to 1988, the office was known as Office of Resident Instruction. As of 1988, the name has been changed to the Office of Academic Programs.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes surveys of graduates and records of the Cornell Office of Resident Instruction.
SUBJECTS
Names:
New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences.; Cornell University -- Administration.; Cornell University -- Admission.; Cornell University -- Students.; New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences. Office of Resident Instruction.
Subjects:
Agriculture -- Societies.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted to permission of office of origin.
CONTAINER LIST
- Admissions Reports, 1934-1945 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Admissions Reports, 1947-1956 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Admissions Reports, 1958-1962 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Annual Report on Admissions, 1966-1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- General Mathematics Test, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Analysis on Cost of Attending the New York State College of Agriculture, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Report on Occupations of the Graduates of the College of Agriculture, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Committee Reports, 1919-1928 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Short Courses in Agriculture, 1892-1942 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Report N.T.S. College of Agriculture to the State University, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Report of Committee on General Education to the Faculty of N.Y.S. College of Agriculture, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Report on Purpose and Objectives of the N.Y.S. College of Agriculture, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Report of Committe on the Educational Program of the College of Agriculture, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Research Program of the College of Agriculture and its Experiment Stations at Ithaca and Geneva, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- New York State College of Agriculture and the Next Quarter Century, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Winton Covey Correspondence, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Campus Academic and Development Plans, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Report by Committee for Reform in the College of Agriculture, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Committee on Educational Policy, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Committee on Educational Policy, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Student Environment Study, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- A Study of Undergraduate Advisees in Science Education, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Honor Council, 1928-1938 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Honor Council, 1946-1958 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Honor Council, 1959-1962 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Agricultural Assembly, 1915-1927 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Intercollegiate Livestock Judging Teams, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Sears Roebuck Scholarship Club of Cornell, 1941-1950 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- H0-Nun-De-Kah Society, 1929-1934 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Heb-Sa Honorary Society, 1912 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- University Faculty, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Helios Society, 1911-1919 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Kermis Club, 1949-1954 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Faculty from College of Agriculture Vital Statistics, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Committee on Registration and Schedules, 1958-1967 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Committee on Registration and Schedules, 1968-1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Universtiy Faculty Calendar Committee, 1945-1968 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Academic Calendar Study, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Special Scholarship Committee, 1939-1951 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Student Work Program, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Student Activities Committee, 1952-1957 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Student Activities Committee, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Disciplinary Action - Newspaper Articles Concerning Student Codes, 1959-1964 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Student Government, 1959-1962 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Reports to Fraternities, 1945-1966 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Student Questionnaire; Report on Student Body, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Report: Factors Related to Application, Registration and Persistence in College, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Attrition Study, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Drop-Outs from College, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Report of the Committee for Study on the Freshman Year, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Report on Student Life at Cornell University, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Comparative Report on Students 1950 and 1962, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Report on Residential Environment, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Report: Committee on General Education for the Four Contract Colleges; Organization of Education in N.Y., 1951 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Report of the Committee on Academic Work and Interest, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Report on the Interdepartmental Program in Biological Science, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Report of the Committee for Academic Affairs, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Report on the Quality of Undergraduate Instruction, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Report on Student-Faculty Relationships, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Report on Undergraduate Education, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Report on Undergraduate Education, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Course Guides, 1950-1964 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Student Evaluation of Teaching and Courses, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Report on Interdependence of University Regulations and Local, State, and Federal Law, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Report on Reorganization of the University Faculty, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Report on the Review of Judicial Procedures for Student Misconduct, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Report of the Special Cornell Commission and Various Other Reports, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Various Reports, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Minutes of University Faculty; Newspaper Articles on Straight Take-Over, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Minutes of the University Faculty, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Memos, Articles, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Plan of the Africana Studies and Research Center at Cornell University, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Newspapaer Articles, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- ROTC Program, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Report of Presidential Commission on Military Training, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Report of Committee on University - ROTC Relations, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Administrative Correspondence, 1915-1958 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- University Development, 1920 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Graduate School of Education, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Inter-College Department of Applied Mathematics, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Admissions Office, 1948-1959 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Admissions Office, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Registrar's Office, 1959-1970 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Roster of Unclassified Students, 1958-1965 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Office of Scholarships and Financial Aid, 1962-1971 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- College of Arts and Sciences, 1961-1964 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- College of Engineering, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Office of the Secretary of the University, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Office of the President, 1963-1971 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Genetics, Physiology and Development, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Public Events Calendar, 1961-1965 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Division of Biological Sciences, 1966-1968 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Division of Biological Sciences, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Reports of Biological Sciences, 1976-1969 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Calendar Committee, 1921-1975 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Campus Traffic, 1930-1975 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Pensions, Insurance, Retirement, 1916-1970 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Student Travel, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Legal Questions - Civil Service, 1914-1971 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Prelaw Advisory Group, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Federal Legislation - General, 1918-1974 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Higher Education Facilities Act, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- University and State Scholarships, 1913-1968 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- State Relations, 1931-1976 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- University Statutes and Orders, 1945-1966 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Heckscher Council, 1920-1942 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- University Trustees, 1960-1974 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Faculty Representation on the Board of Trustees, 1920-1956 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Endowment Funds, 1923-1950 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Patents, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Athletics, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Military Science and Naval R.O.T.C., 1931-1975 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- University Press, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Publications List of Resident Instruction, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Dean of Women, 1935-1945 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- National Youth Administration Student Aid Program, 1935-1942 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Tenure, 1945-1970 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Tenure Proceedures, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Hospital and Medical Care, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- State Legislation, 1960-1968 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Visiting Scholars, 1954-1967 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Legislation of the Faculty of the New York State College of Agriculture, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- University Faculty Minutes, 1960-1965 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- University Faculty Minutes, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Commencement, 1960-1968 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- University Senate, 1969-1973 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Cornell University Council, 1962-1970 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Cornell University Placement Service, 1963-1969 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Deans Conferences, 1948-1951 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Council of Student Personnel Associates, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Administrative Boards and Advisory Councils, 1960-1964 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Dean of Students, 1963-1973 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Cornell Centennial, 1960-1965 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Cornell University Policy on Release of Student Records, 1968-1973 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- University Moving Costs, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Courses for Employees, 1968-1970 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Organization of College of Agriculture, 1915-1958 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Budget Items for Office of Resident Instruction, 1967-1969 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Organization Chart - Office of Resident Instruction, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Functions of Office of Director Of Resident Instruction, 1930-1973 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Office of Resident Instruction Inventories, 1948-1961 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Office of Resident Instruction Maintenance - Salaries, 1911-1949 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Relations with the Business Office, 1914-1935 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Classification of Employees, 1930-1949 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Office of Resident Instruction Job Descriptions, 1945-1969 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Office of Resident Instruction Reports, 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Office of Resident Instruction Floor Plans, 1960-1963 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Office of Resident Instruction Admissions Office, 1964-1972 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Resident Instruction, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Resident Instruction Programs, 1964-1968 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Program for Advisory Council Meeting, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Administrative Organization of Cornell University College of Agriculture, 1926-1959 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Organization in Other Institutions, 1916-1921 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- College of Agriculture Advisory Council, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Advisory Council Meeting Program for the College of Agriculture, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- College of Agriculture Advisory Council, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Agricultural College Council Minutes, 1950-1960 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Agricultural College Council Minutes, 1960-1963 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Agricultural College Council Minutes, 1964-1969 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Agricultural College Council Minutes, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- State College Council, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- State College Council, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- State College Council, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Appropriations - Gifts, 1910-1949 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- College Budget - Allocation of Funds, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Budget Data, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Federal Teaching Funds, 1945-1961 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Fees, Tuition - Accessory Instruction, 1950-1971 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Report for State University - Dean Kennedy, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Teaching Assistants, 1062-1965 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Policy - Undergraduate Teaching Aides, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Advisory Committee, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Teaching Assistants, 1966-1968 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Graduate Assistants Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Teaching Assistants, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Graduate Assistants Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Federal Teaching Funds, 1962-1970 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Advisory Committee to Review Teaching Assistants, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Report of Advisory Committee on Graduate Assistants, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Teaching Assistants Financing Procedures, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Teaching Loads by Departments, 1968-1970 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Advisory Committee for Premedical and Predental Students, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Dedication of Building Plans, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Campus Plans and Maps, 1910-1971 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Buildings - Use of Lands, 1911-1973 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Buildings - Capitol Construction, 1961-1972 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Smith-Hughes Funds - General, 1929-1938 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Cost of Accessory Instruction, 1930-1970 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Payment for Instruction, 1912-1918 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Payment for Instruction, 1919-1925 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Payment for Instruction, 1925-1930 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Payment for Instruction, 1930-1933 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Payment for Instruction, 1933-1936 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Payment for Instruction, 1936-1943 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Payment for Instruction, 1943-1949 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Payment for Instruction, 1949-1955 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Payment for Instruction, 1955-1969 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Accessory Instruction Assignments, 1967-1969 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Accessory Instruction Assignments, 1971-1974 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- General Education Board, 1926-1929 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Institute of International Education, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- American Council on Education, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Undergraduate Programs - Colleges of Agriculture, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- SUNY Graduate Council, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- State University of New York, 1951-1976 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- State Relations, 1972-1975 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- SUNY Faculty Grants for Improvement of Undergraduate Instruction, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Courses in Biological Sciences and Accessory Instruction, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Course Coordination and Personnel Echange Committee for Region II, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- SUNY 25th Anniversary Campus Open House, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- SUNY Region II - Admissions and Transfer, 1968-1975 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- SUNY Central Awards Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- SUNY Central Awards Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- SUNY Central Awards Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- SUNY Central Awards Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- SUNY General Policy for Tuition Wavier for Employees, 1969-1973 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- SUNY Faculty Senate, 1952-1976 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- SUNY Student Affairs, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- SUNY Campus Academic Plan, 1965-1973 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Special Enrollment Projections, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Reports on SUNY Questionnaire, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Master Plan for State Regents, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Responses to Campus Academic Plan, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- SUNY Chancellor's Awards for Exellence in Teaching, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- James Stouffer - Nominee for Chancellor's Award, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Robert Mower - Nominee for Chancellor's Award, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Robert Clausen - Nominee for Chancellor's Award, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Joseph Bugliari - Nominee for Chancellor's Award, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Harlan Banks - Nominee for Chancellor's Award, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- SUNY Master Plan, 1968-1976 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Campus Enrollment Growth, 1969-1986 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- State Experiment Station at Geneva, 1922-1976 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Travel - Transportation Costs, 1956-1970 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Women's Compensation, 1929-1939 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Fellowships, Scholarships, 1930-1970 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Danforth Foundation, 1929-1974 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Guggenheim Foundation, 1926-1927 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- International Harvester Scholarships, 1931 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- National Research Fellowships, 1932-1947 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- SUNY Chancellor, 1967-1969 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Harvard Scoiety of Fellows, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Graduate Fellowships, 1915-1969 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Roberts Scholarships, 1920-1926 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Non-Resident Scholarships, 1926-1973 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Industrial Fellowships, 1921-1937 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- New York State Banker's Association, 1926-1959 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Beatty Scholarships (Winter Course), 1919-1940 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Robert Adams Scholarships, 1938-1952 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Jewish Agricultural Society, 1921-1957 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Devastated Countries, 1920 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Morris Fair Association Scholarship, 1930-1949 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Grange League Federation, 1927-1936 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Grange Scholarships, 1919-1923 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- American Agriculturist Scholarships, 1922-1923 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Clinton Dewitt Smith Fellowships, 1931-1945 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Hervey S. Hall Scholarships, 1931-1945 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- New York Florists Club Scholarships, 1931-1944 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Phi Kappa Phi and Knickerbacker Bursaries, 1928-1955 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Scholarship, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Delano Scholarships, 1936-1942 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- George F. Warren Scholarships, 1956-1969 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Annie M. Hatch Scholarships, 1936-1967 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Denison Henry Strong Medical Foundation, 1938-1947 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Sears-Roebuck Agricultural Scholarships, 1940-1968 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Abraham Eller Fund, 1938-1939 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Tuition Scholarship in the Graduate School, 1932-1974 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Ullman Trust, 1952-1967 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Morganthau Fellowship, 1926-1927 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- New York Federation of Women's Clubs, 1936-1939 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Borden Agricultural Scholarships, 1944-1969 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Rite-Way Scholarships, 1945-1948 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Burpee Award in Horticulture (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Albert R. Brand Scholarships, 1945-1953 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Women's National Farm and Garden Scholarships, 1941-1969 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Carl E. Ladd Memorial Scholarship, 1947-1966 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- George Lamont Educational Fund, 1943-1972 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Harold E. Gulvin Scholarships of the Lincoln Foundation, 1946-1953 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- ESSO 4-H Scholarships, 1947-1969 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Ward W. Stevens Scholarships, 1949-1964 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- New york State Baby Chick Association 4-H Scholarships, 1947-1951 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Heatley Green Scholarship Fund, 1948-1955 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Leland Spencer Dairy Marketing Research Scholarships, 1949-1967 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- National Association of Thoroughbred Breeders Scholarships, 1950-1952 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- New york State Canners and Freezers Association Scholarships, 1950-1964 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Morrison Fellowship in Livestock Feeding, 1950-1967 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Hudson H. Lyon Scholarship Fund for Agricultural Missionaries, 1950-1969 (Box 9, Folder 39)
- Julian E. Butterworth Research Fellowships, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 40)
- Paul R. Guldin Memorial Endowment, 1950-1968 (Box 9, Folder 41)
- Van Dale Farm Machines Scholarships, 1952-1955 (Box 9, Folder 42)
- Arvie Eldred Scholarships, 1953-1968 (Box 9, Folder 43)
- Walter R. Clarke Memorial Scholarships, 1953-1955 (Box 9, Folder 44)
- Cornell Dairy Science Association Scholarships, 1954-1964 (Box 9, Folder 45)
- Ralston Purina Scholarships, 1955-1969 (Box 9, Folder 46)
- Cornell-Swedish Exchange Scholarships, 1954-1967 (Box 9, Folder 47)
- William Frederick Dreer Scholarships, 1955-1969 (Box 9, Folder 48)
- Cornell Pomology Scholarships, 1956-1969 (Box 9, Folder 49)
- Alfred C. Hottes Amateur Gardening Scholarship, 1956-1962 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- National Plant Food Institute Agronomy Achievement Award, 1956-1968 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Dairymen's League Agricultural Scholarships, 1957-1969 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Eastern Frosted Foods Association Scholarships, 1958-1970 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- New York Lime Association Scholarship, 1957-1968 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Laura L. Barnes Scholarship, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Cornell Poultry Club Scholarship, 1958-1964 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- New York State Turf Association Scholarships, 1958-1960 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Sillas Dairy Scholarship Fund, 1958-1959 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Federated Garden Clubs of New York State Scholarships, 1958-1969 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Frank B. Morrison Memorial Scholarships, 1958-1969 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Regents Scholarships, 1958-1965 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Henry H. Buckley Foundation Scholarships, 1959-1969 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- New York Farmer's Scholarships, 1936-1972 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Eastern Milk Producers Cooperative Association Scholarships, 1959-1967 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Frank W. Mason Agricultural Scholarships, 1959-1967 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Cladakis Scholarships, 1945-1966 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Louis Ware Scholarship-Fellowship Fund, 1960-1968 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Marion A. and A. Percy Leon Scholarships, 1960-1967 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Edmond Sawtell Scholarships, 1957-1963 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Cornell-Argentine Exchange Scholarships, 1961-1971 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Western New York Section of the Institute of Food Technologists Award, 1961-1968 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Leonard A. Dudley Scholarships, 1962-1969 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- C. Edwin Dimon Scholarships, 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- National Merit Scholarships, 1963-1969 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Dyson Foundation Scholarships, 1962-1974 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- H.J. Heinz Company Scholarships, 1962-1969 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Nopco Chemical Company Scholarships, 1961-1967 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- General Food Scholarships, 1962-1973 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- National Food Brokers Association Scholarships, 1962-1969 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Woodrow Wilson National Fellowships, 1963-1969 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Fulbright Student Scholarships, 1962-1972 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Sara Lee Company Scholarships, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Robert N. Marshall Memorial Poultry Scholarships, 1963-1967 (Box 10, Folder 34)
- French Food Technology Awards, 1963-1967 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Marshall Scholarships in Britain, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- W.S.Middaugh - Alpha Zeta Memorial Scholarships, 1964-1972 (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Burton A. Jennings Memorial Endowment Fund, 1965-1969 (Box 10, Folder 38)
- John F. Kennedy Memorial Scholarships, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 39)
- Jewel T. Foundation Scholarships, 1965-1969 (Box 10, Folder 40)
- Oscar Mayer Foundation Scholarships, 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 41)
- May Walker Agricultural Scholarships, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 42)
- Gerber Scholarships in Horticulture, 1965-1969 (Box 10, Folder 43)
- Borden Scholarship Award in Food Distribution, 1965-1969 (Box 10, Folder 44)
- Campbell Soup Company Scholarships, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 45)
- New York Florists Club Award in Floriculture, 1966-1969 (Box 10, Folder 46)
- Food Distribution Industry Scholarships, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 47)
- Rohm and Haas Company Scholarships, 1966-1972 (Box 10, Folder 48)
- Cornell-Monterrey Exchange Scholarships, 1966-1968 (Box 10, Folder 49)